Guide to the School of Management, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Clayton P. Alderfer, 1969-1997; Accession 2016-A-059
  Restricted until January 1, 2027
  - Course Materials
    - AD SCI 523a Intergroup Relations in Organizations, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Gay/straight literature and teaching, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Financial analysis and management project schedules, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Fall term courses, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Individual and Group Behavior (IGB) administrative memos, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - IGB class lists, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - IGB community building, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - IGB community building-course designs, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - IGB community building exercises, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - IGB course evaluations, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
    - IGB grades, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - IGB grades and course evaluations, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - IGB learning contract, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - IGB organizations, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - IGB organizations, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - IGB organizations-course critiques, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
    - IGB papers
      - "Afunious", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - "Globetrotters", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - "The Good Prospects", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - "The Independent Variable", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - "Just Plain Spokes", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - "There be Dragons", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - IGB preparation, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - IGB race, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - IGB section enrollment, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - IGB staff, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - IGB units
      - Unit 1: Teaching introduction, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Unit 2: Adult Development, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Unit 3: Intragroup Dynamics, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Unit 4: Leadership Styles, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Unit 5: Intergroup Dynamics-Motto, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Unit 6: Race and Ethnic Relations, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Unit 7: Gender, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - IGB written assignments-originals, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Professional Files
    - Berkeley conference, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - CEGO lecture-discussion series, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence-general
      - 1973-1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence-faculty and personnel, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Curriculum Committee-second year, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Curriculum review, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Exchange article, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - First New Haven National Bank-organizational study, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - George Williams workshop, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Health services proposal, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - School of Management-history and drafts, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Lectures and speeches-notes and correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda to the interim board, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Oregon conference, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Ph.D. program memorandum, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - The Phoenix Indian School-reports and research materials, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Project 60 report, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Taft School research report, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - University of Virginia trip, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - School of Management records
    - General files
      - 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Academic calendar, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Admissions, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Administrative science curriculum development-correspondence and documentation, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative action, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Alumni, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Alumni board of directors, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Alumni correspondence and ephemera, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Alumni session feedback, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Alumni report: "Birth of the School" by William S. Beinecke, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Alumni newsletter, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Alumni survey, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Annual report, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Assistant Director of Professional Studies (ADPS)
      - ADPS counseling report, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - ADPS job activities report, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - ADPS student interest groups report, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - ADPS tutoring report, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - ADPS special projects committee, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Black People in in Management Schools-presentation, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Campus dedication ephemera, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Charter class facebook, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Charter class wrap-up meeting, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Class of 1982-correspondence and ephemera (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Class of 1984-correspondence and ephemera (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Class of 1989-commencement ephemera and correspondence (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Community day, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Class of 1990-commencement ephemera (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Community building, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence
      - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - 1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - 1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - 1982 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - 1982 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - 1983 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - 1983 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - 1984 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - 1984 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - 1984-1990 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence-Benno Schimidt, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence-Mike Levine, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence-Mike Levine, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - CPO policy on Ph.D. people, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Curriculum
      - 1976 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Curriculum Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Curriculum Committee report, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Curriculum Committee report, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Darden School of Business-reports and policy studies, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Debriefing meeting-Class of 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Director of Professional Studies-correspondence and reports, 1979-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Discipline Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - DPS material-David Morgan, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - DPS staff job description, 1978-1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Doctoral program-academic guidelines, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Doctoral review, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Educational Materials Development Center (EMDC), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Evaluation of teaching performance, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Faculty committee report, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Faculty time/workload, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Faculty/student advisors, 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Internship dialogue, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Internships, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Jepson School of Leadership Studies, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Joint degrees, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Liasion meetings
      - 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Liasion meeting minutes
        - 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 20)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 21)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Local 34 union drive/organizing, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Minority experience at SOM-study, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - News and events, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Organizational behavior (OB)-correspondence, notes and ephemera, 1989-1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - OB doctoral program, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - OB partner's day, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - OB story, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Policy sciences institute, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Ph.D program-Milgrom's memo, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Registrar/Assistant Registrar-personnel, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Review of OB junior faculty, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Second term questionnaire, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - SOM budget, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - SOM partners-Class of 1985, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - "SOM Student" newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Strike, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Student workload and course evaluations, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Write-up of second year curriculum, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Yale management Partner's Day, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Yale College, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 44)